I become so numb I can't feel you there
become so ti so much
more I'm becoming this all I want to do
is
[Applause]
[Music]
be B leby do you have any dreams dreams
oh [__] you know I have money if I want
something I just make like the boy band
and sink and bye bye bye haha oh
Bartleby that's not quite what I meant
then enlighten me love do you have a
dream he he well I do but it's a weav at
embarrassing oh do you want me to spank
you uhhuh have you ever heard of the
Nickelodeon game show Legends of the
Hidden Temple nope well it was a game
show that Nickelodeon hosted and kids
would race through a temple and put
together a silver monkey to win
prizes that sounds [__]
stupid well I suppose it does sound a
little silly but to tell you the truth I
always wanted to be a part of it it just
looked so much fun if only that game
show wasn't canceled all those years ago
well your dream might come to fruition
my beach if you just keep
dreaming
what the [__] why are all of these
shirts
blue my is that a
problem lingo did you do this where's
all my gry shirts with the Indie bands
on them I threw them out they were
getting really
stinky you idiot you told me you were
bagging them up because they look cool
well I lied [__] now find something to
wear the food Pantry closes at noon and
I want to beat Lawrence there you know
how he takes multiple cans of beans when
the sign only says to take
one looks like someone's been putting on
a bit of weight you nasty little piggy
hey SLE have you noticed that your hair
is kind of blue like Sonic the
Hedgehog hey SLE have you noticed your
hair is kind of blue like Sonic the
Hedgehog shut up [__] I only DED it
like this because you said he would make
me look
[Music]
cool hey if you get fat you would look
even more like Sonic wouldn't that be
funny I guess it is pretty funny how he
might die of diabetes yeah haha hey
isn't it cool that I have yellow hair
like ble bonic is so
cool you [__] [__] I see what you're
trying to
do you're trying to turn us into Bargain
Bin Sonic and Bartleby where you get to
be the cool one good luck [__] all of
your clothes that aren't blue are
already over there in a box to donate to
Goodwill so put that shirt back on
before I
[__] wait to mobious minute your IQ is
literally 37 why am I listening to your
ass because I'm 980b and can crush your
whole body like a
pineapple sleep look a yellow piece of
paper do you think it tastes like cheese
dear sleep and dumbass they got your
name wrong that is my real name SLE and
dumbass you are cordially invited to
take part in the return of the hit
nickin game show Legends of the Hidden
Temple this contest will be comprised of
two challenges the first one being who
can put together than damn silver monkey
that somehow nobody knows how to do and
the second event where three contestants
will raise to climb the the AGR
Crag wait a minute the AGR Crag wasn't
even a part of Legends of the Hidden
Temple it was a totally separate game
show call
guts Bart lebby have you ever even
watched Legends of the Hidden Temple are
you accusing me [__] go entertain me
because if I am not entertained you are
sleeping in the dogghouse out
[Music]
back
nice to see you nice to see you all
thank you very much for being here yeah
welcome to the Legends of the Hidden
Temple Legends of the Hidden Temple
where rooms are filled with lost
treasures and of course the One of a
Kind silver monkey that is being
protected by mysterious rapists I mean
my in Temple
Gods yeah one of these three teams will
have the chance to solve the puzzles and
walk away with the grand prize 20 whole
dolls to our back steakouse will it be
the green
monkeys the red
Jaguars and last but not least the
purple
barretts race through the temple you
might want to sit out for this one bro
what are you trying to say that you're
faster than me this ain't like the old
days and you know it you're overweight
now look at Trevor over there even he's
faster than you and his [__] legs
look like like
noodles so stand back and watch Knuckles
the cool kidna but I'm I'm Sonic the
Hedgehog I'm sorry you had to find out
like this but you're [__] fat and I'm
not talking about that absolute dumb
truck of an ass you may look in the
mirror and see Sonic the fastest thing
alive but to the rest of us you're just
Sonic the fat [__] who eats the last
slice of pizza every time we order from
Pizza Hut
I thought you guys always left it for me
on
purpose is that what you actually
believe or is that what you tell
yourself it's what I tell
myself Al righty Al righty my [__]
which of you three are willing to Brave
the Hidden Temple first the other three
will be climbing the egro cck in round
two perfect now when I say go you're
going to rise through the temple Gates
and make your way to the treasure rooms
if a rapist I mean a temple guard drags
you out of the temple you're
disqualified on your mark get
set
yeah which way should we go first why
are you asking us yellow [__] we're all
on separate teams I was only saying
because this place is full of rapists I
mean Temple guards so I believe we
should watch one another's asses shut up
we both saw sagging that nerd with a
glass is you're are just a [__] who's got
his eyes on our cool guy buts well that
is simply a false accusation damn
it holy crap
Knuckles what that's one of the three
pieces of the silver monkey where did
you find that we were only in the temple
for like 15 seconds while you twink
little were being gay I du under the
ground and found a secret chamber you
can't dig under the ground I'm Manaka
it's what we do damn I knew that I just
never saw one actually do it before hey
that's not fair if life was fair it
wouldn't have made to men face the wrath
of Knuckles the cool
kid see you around [__] sleep we have
to work together why the [__] do you
have an afro there's no way we're going
to win against him if we don't you know
what I hate to admit it but you're right
no I'm yellow and just like that
Knuckles the EG CH has just found his
second treasure piece only one more
piece to go and the purple barretts win
round one Bo keep it up damn it Cyrus
you're making us look like
clowns H just as I suspected I will be
facing off with the nerd in round two
well one thing certain there's only one
thing that stands in the way of me
getting to the top of the Agro CAG and
winning this game show and it's you
Trevor my rival in this
[__] look at them standing there they
know exactly what they're doing pointing
their butts sour way remember all we are
supposed to do is grab them nothing
sexual do you understand me Danny y y I
hear you shut the [__] up I don't thank
you to Danny what did I say to get some
ass come
here that's what you giving me yeah
don't you push me [__] he's fighting
back get the pepper
spray s help
me sleep we had a deal don't let him
take me away haha foolish Tri there's
nothing else he can do sleep would never
turn his back on the Outback Steakhouse
Victory belongs to the green M hold on
cus I'm
coming
[Applause]
[Music]
yo what the [__] this room gay as
hell well well well look what we have
here you guys found the last silver
monkey piece and you're going to give it
to me how generous of your ass Knuckles
please
don't what's wrong [__] it's only a
scratch
[Applause]
I don't think you'll be needing this
anymore or
this thanks for making my job easy
[__] I'd give you a pat on the ass
but I'm not
gay it's official while the man guards
were capturing two of the contestants
Knuckles located and put together all
three pieces of the silver monkey that
means the purple barretts officially win
round one W yeah we will get back to you
after we send in some cops to arrest
those Temple guards and figure out their
sexual assault charges yeah ladies and
gentlemen the competition has been very
hot now it's going to get even hotter
because now folks we're at the aggro cck
three men will battle it out for one
piece of the crack up top but only one
can walk away with the prize it all
comes down to this
awesome what's the matter Beach
intimidated perhaps I am a wh SM don't
be my love remember what you told me
it's been your dream since you were 3
years old and considering how old you
are it's been your dream
for how old are you again 15 it's been
your dream for 22 years don't let that
dream die now that you're finally here
hey shrimp no don't hit me what I didn't
come over here to beat your ass you're
not listen nerd I know I murdered your
parents in Cold Blood after they broke
into robotnik's house trying to rape
[Music]
him
but it's time I tell you the truth the
truth of what really happened that night
then go you mustn't I have to [__] now
that I am no longer tied up in the
chains of evil this boy deserves to know
what really happened not the story
Robotnik wants him to believe I know
what happened you killed my
parents no I saved you like a hero like
he man and his boyfriend man at r
arms oh I can't wait for tonight can you
my sweet honey pot
pie what happens tonight
[__] you didn't forget did you it's when
we become rich as [__] oh yeah after we
break into Dr robotnik's house and drae
him we are going to sell our own son
into sex slavery to the celebrity Bill
[__] Cosby for
$600 oh boy I can't wait we can finally
buy an Xbox series X and play cyberpunk
77 SLE did you hear that yeah I did that
game is [__] trash they're going to
sell their own son into sex slavery How
could a mother and father even think of
doing such a thing well $600 is like
seven or a full price games we need to
do something oh no we don't think face
if robot Nick found out we would be
kicked to the curb you're right s I'm
sorry for thinking for myself and that's
what happened after your parents broke
into robotnik's house he called me to
come rescue his big round butt I knew I
could take the opportunity to not only
keep my job but Save You by tossing you
out of the four-story window I don't
believe this I thought my parents loved
me oh you poor baby
oh Trevor I'm so
sorry thanks Cyrus now it makes sense
they never let me leave out of the house
it's because they didn't want people to
know I existed they told me the reason
was because I was a vampire and I
believed them because I was [__]
stupid that was why I like the movie
morbius because it hits so close to home
now I know I just have bad taste in
movies thanks for telling me this dingo
I'm glad we can do what Israel and
Palestine did not and put the past
behind us no hard feelings you got hit
nerd let's have ourselves a fair
game 2
1 happy
year this isn't fair my partner is so
fat he can't even get over the first
step haha I'm doing it Cyrus I'm in
first
place not for long hey nerd are you
Jewish no why because here comes the
gas what are you lying around for you
know how much I had to spend for this
game show put a fire under that behind
and climb the stupid rock already I'm
sorry Bartleby but the shut
up please the other two contestants are
so much stronger and faster than me I
guess some dreams just aren't meant to
come true after
all I see you're enjoying this you dirty
little [__] then again I'm
too Trevor Dango I don't get it why are
you helping my round ass because you
reminded us us that love matters I don't
get it if it wasn't for you bringing us
here me and trer would have never made
up if anyone deserves to stand at the
top of the aroc CAG it's the one and
only Sonic the
Hedgehog all
right W
yeah H who are you [__] I'm Robert Toro
oh my God Robert Toro who is Robert Toro
he's the first ever person to clim AR
frag on the game show gut that's right
I'm not surprised you don't know
anything about me Sonic after becoming
Victorious and reaching the Pinnacle of
Triumph I did nothing with my life but
now I can finally do something that
would put me on National Television TV
again before I die and that's to present
you with this PR
a piece of the
[Applause]
[Music]
Craig
you did it [__] you proved to the whole
world that it is possible to achieve
your fuckling dreams all you have to do
is be rich or no a rich person like
me if I tonight if I am sad
tonight I don't have a job to find and
if I work tonight if I'm so tired
tonight I'll fall fall asleep when I'm
home when I'm
[Applause]
[Music]
home I was just so far from here focused
on my own way with the Never back to
those wo Liv and fear there was nothing
I could do there is nothing you said
that could make me realize I'm a luy I
was just Out Of Reach on the fire was
not aare my now but when I stop to see I
speaking for speaking for oh just need
to open my eyes now to try to change
them to be someone among other I've got
to try if I be tonight if I tonight I
don't have to J Too
F my
tonight
[Music]